对于我们来说
For us,
查询将是最复杂的所需的content provider的方法
query will be the most complex of
the required content provider methods.
我们已经给你了实现操作的大致框架
We've given you the bones,
of the query operation.
如你所见 使用我们拥有的SURI的对象
As you can see,
we use our SURI nature object,
再对URI的类型进行判断
once again to switch on the type of URI.
需要注意的是 这个方法每次都会返回一个cursor对象来
Note that each response from this
function, will return a cursor that
对应你要查询的那个URI
corresponds to the incoming
query as defined by the URI.
这是唯一的方法我们必须填写不同的
This is the only function where we
will have to fill out a different
返回内容为每一个类型的URI在content provider中
response for every type of
URI in the content provider,
他们中的一些可能只用于查询
as several of them
are used in queries only.
在这个方法的底部，我们将设置通知为
At the bottom of our function, we're
going to set the notification URI for
我们的传给这个方法的对应的cursor的URI
our cursor to the one that
was passed into the function.
这使cursor注册一个content observer，来守望
This causes the cursor to register
a content observer, to watch for
那个URI的以及任何的子URI发生的变化
changes that happen to that URI and
any of its descendants.
这让content provider很容易的告诉UI 当cursor
This allows the content provider,
to easily tell the UI when the cursor
改变的时候 类似数据库中的插入或者查询操作
changes, on operations like
a database insert or update.
稍后我们会看到更多 当我们讨论插入和
We'll see more on this later,
when we cover inserting and
更新数据库的时候
updating the database.
取消注释掉test provider中的基本的天气查询方法和
Uncomment the test basic weather query
function within test provider and
运行代码当你完成的时候，并且要保证所有这些运行正常
run this code when you're finished, to
make sure all of this is working well.